profitzon.com 2012-03-02

# Deadbeat Super Affiliate

Deadbeat Super Affiliate Privacy Policy

**DeadbeatSuperAffiliate.com** (the 'site') is owned and operated by Daniel Brock (the 'company'). By using this site, you agree to the collection and use of your information by use in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Do not use this site if you don't agree with this Privacy Policy!

**Changes to policy**

We reserve the right to change, modify, and amend this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. It is recommended that you check back with this page to make sure you still agree with the policy.

**Service Providers**

When you become a member by purchasing our products or services, or use any other features on this website, we request that you provide financial information such as account or credit card numbers ('Financial Information'). Will will use your Financial Information to bill you for products and services and process your transactions. By making a purchase on this website, you consent to our sharing your Personally Identifiable Information and Financial Information with our services providers and to such third parties that we determine are necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include, but not limited to, credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction. We prohibit these third parties from using your Personally Identifiable Information for any other purposes. We may use third party contractors to help us operator our business and adminster activities on our behalf, such as credit card transactions, and may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes.

**Order Confirmation**

When ordering our products or services, we may share your Personally Identifiable Information you provide on our confirmation page with a select group of third party marketing partners with similiar products and services you may be interested in. We only work with partners who contractually agree to offer you the ability to opt-out of receiving future offers, and also contractually agree not to share your information with others. Our third party marketing parters are separate from this website, so therefore we are not responsible for their content or offers. If you do not wish for your information to be shared with our marketing partners, please do not order our products or contact us at the address below.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our policies, please contact us below:

Daniel Brock  
101 Yorkleigh Road  
Baltimore, MD 21204

Effective Date: October 10th, 2010
